<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Eira Hazel</title>
        <link>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Eira Hazel</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:09:30 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Meetings</title>
    <link>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/meetings/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:09:30 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Eira Hazel</author>
    <guid>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/meetings/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Nothing in the world is more tedious than attending meetings. On a perfectly fine day, a crowd of people is forced to drop their urgent, important, and interesting tasks to gather under one roof. All this, just to listen to three or five people flex their rhetorical muscles, arguing over matters that are discussed without decision, decided without execution, or executed without success. It is truly the ultimate method of collective time-wasting.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Space Delivery Service</title>
    <link>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/space-express/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:30:45 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Eira Hazel</author>
    <guid>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/space-express/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Seeing people hyping up <strong>space delivery</strong> services is genuinely hard to take seriously. Do some Chinese people have a bizarre obsession with the title of &ldquo;Infrastructure Maniac&rdquo;? Anyone who thinks this can replace standard courier services like SF Express should seriously retake high school physics, or at least solve a couple of mechanics problems before asking such a ridiculous question.</p>
<p>Just think about it: what kind of functionally <strong>low-IQ product manager</strong> would come up with this requirement? Raising the cost by tens of thousands of times just to shave off an hour or two? Doesn&rsquo;t physics deserve some respect? Do you understand <strong>G-force</strong>? The vibration during launch is so intense that if you shipped a MacBook, the screen would probably shatter into dust. Then you&rsquo;d have to wrap the package in three layers of aerospace-grade cushioning material. Isn&rsquo;t that the definition of <strong>flogging a dead horse</strong> (Chinese: 脱裤子放屁, literally: pulling down pants to fart)?</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>After Labels Fail</title>
    <link>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/after-labels-fail/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:22:18 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Eira Hazel</author>
    <guid>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/after-labels-fail/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>People nowadays seem to have lost the ability to process &ldquo;high-fidelity information.&rdquo; The brain&rsquo;s GPU computing power simply isn&rsquo;t enough to run high-load processes like &ldquo;independent thinking.&rdquo;</p>
<p>What the vast majority of typical Chinese people need is just a Tag, a compressed residue.</p>
<p>For example: Huawei equals patriotism or an intelligence tax, Xiaomi equals losers, and Apple equals traitors.</p>
<p>Once a Tag is slapped on, the brain gets comfortable and stops spinning. These people are like a broken LLM: input a token, and it only spits out those few fixed characters with the highest probability.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Deploying Hugo Blog to GitHub Pages</title>
    <link>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/deploy-to-github-pages/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:30:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Eira Hazel</author>
    <guid>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/deploy-to-github-pages/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h1 id="deploying-hugo-blog-to-github-pages">Deploying Hugo Blog to GitHub Pages</h1>
<p>This guide explains how to deploy your Hugo blog to GitHub Pages for free hosting.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Note: This is a placeholder for translation. The complete translation will be added later.</p></blockquote>
<h2 id="setting-up-your-github-repository">Setting Up Your GitHub Repository</h2>
<p>Create a repository named <code>yourusername.github.io</code> to host your blog.</p>
<h2 id="configuring-github-actions">Configuring GitHub Actions</h2>
<p>Use GitHub Actions to automate the build and deployment process of your Hugo site.</p>
<h2 id="custom-domain-configuration">Custom Domain Configuration</h2>
<p>Learn how to set up a custom domain for your GitHub Pages site.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Hugo Blog CRUD Operations Guide</title>
    <link>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/blog-crud-guide/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:25:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Eira Hazel</author>
    <guid>https://nothingness0db.github.io/posts/blog-crud-guide/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h1 id="hugo-blog-crud-operations-guide">Hugo Blog CRUD Operations Guide</h1>
<p>This guide covers the basic Create, Read, Update, and Delete operations for managing content on your Hugo blog.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Note: This is a placeholder for translation. The complete translation will be added later.</p></blockquote>
<h2 id="creating-new-content">Creating New Content</h2>
<p>Hugo provides simple commands to create new content for your blog.</p>
<h2 id="reading-content">Reading Content</h2>
<p>Learn how to properly structure and organize your content for easy navigation.</p>
<h2 id="updating-content">Updating Content</h2>
<p>Discover the best practices for updating existing content while maintaining SEO.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
